{
    "id": "536256bacfa344d49131c976388a3b78",
    "title": "Simple Past Or Past Participle",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It has been years since I last ………………… him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "saw",
                "seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "060b36c043a94b7b8492cf085bf06352"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………. better days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "saw",
                "seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0106db1894b40adb5b18cac48a7a962"
        },
        {
            "question": "Marathi is ………………….. in the Deccan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "spoke",
                "spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c11bcd0a758b40e494c20627fdcb05c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The inscription has ..................... away in several places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wear",
                "wore",
                "worn"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b7d51a1bf36f4626b14104d6b2b058be"
        },
        {
            "question": "The country is …………………. by factions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tear",
                "tore",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f808fa914de45ad8afdd2f45d71352d"
        },
        {
            "question": "In a fit of rage, she ………………… up the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tear",
                "tore",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7494ca658acb467b8036b95af4b6ea69"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. for his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "ran"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20ebd0b8037e42b18723a68d3c7bdf5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look as if you ……………….. all the way home",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "ran"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bf72f07ecc24b0f9990c87e4e028990"
        },
        {
            "question": "We could not have ……………….. a better day for the drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chose",
                "choose",
                "chosen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36589ffeca1d41038d837ed0cd8f2c48"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old beggar was ………………… by a mad dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bit",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b29ad7e82a542448d64c3dde6932ee0"
        }
    ]
}